{
  "numOfQs": 10,
  "title": "History Quiz",
  "quizitems": [{
    "questiontext":"Which country did Germany invade on the 1st of September 1939?",
    "answertext":"Poland",
    "choices":["France",    
     "Czechoslovakia",
     "Poland",
     "Finland"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"What was the first country to give women the vote in 1893?",
    "answertext":"New Zealand",
    "choices":["America",    
     "Australia",
     "New Zealand",
     "Iceland"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"What is the oldest known story in the world?",
    "answertext":"The Epic of Gilgamesh",
    "choices":["The Bible",    
     "The Histories",
     "The Epic of Gilgamesh",
     "The Odyssey"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Which of these was one of the seven ancient wonders of the world?",
    "answertext":"Lighthouse of Alexandria",
    "choices":["Great Wall of China",    
     "Macchu Picchu",
     "Lighthouse of Alexandria",
     "Taj Mahal"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"In 1066 at the Battle of Hastings, King Harold was defeated by:",
    "answertext":"William",
    "choices":["Harald",    
     "William",
     "Tostig",
     "Ragnar"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Sliced bread was invented in:",
    "answertext":"America in 1928",
    "choices":["America in 1928",    
     "France in 1789",
     "Australia in 1897",
     "Scotland in 1902"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"What year did the Berlin Wall fall?",
    "answertext":"1989",
    "choices":["1988",    
     "1994",
     "1991",
     "1989"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Who was Garibaldi?",
    "answertext":"A famous Italian soldier",
    "choices":["A famous Italian painter",    
     "A famous Italian soldier",
     "A famous Italian chef",
     "A famous Italian monk"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"In which country was the French Revolution of 1789?",
    "answertext":"France",
    "choices":["Mexico",    
     "Germany",
     "Italy",
     "France"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Who was said to be so beautiful that her face launched a thousand ships?",
    "answertext":"Helen",
    "choices":["Cleopatra",    
     "Helen",
     "Nefertiti",
     "Salome"]
  }]   
}